Guide to the Department of Epidemiology and Public Health, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Departmental Files, 1940-1960; Series I
  - 1955-1956
    - American Social Hygiene Association, 1956 (Box 240, Folder 2575)
    - Boy Scouts of America, 1955-1956 (Box 240, Folder 2576)
      - Quinnipiac Council, 1955-1956 (Box 240, Folder 2577)
    - Civil Defense: local, state and national, 1956 (Box 240, Folder 2578)
    - Cleveland Health Museum, 1955-1956 (Box 241, Folder 2579)
    - Community Chests and Councils of America, 1955-1956 (Box 241, Folder 2582)
    - National Budget Committee, 1955-1956 (Box 241, Folder 2583)
    - National Budget Committee, 1955-1956 (Box 242, Folder 2584-2585)
      - Panel 1, 1955-1956 (Box 242, Folder 2586)
    - Connecticut Advisory Council on School Health, 1955-1956 (Box 242, Folder 2587)
    - Connecticut Health League, 1955-1956 (Box 242, Folder 2588)
    - Connecticut Public Health Association, 1955-1956 (Box 242, Folder 2589)
    - Connecticut Public Health Nursing Association, 1955-1956 (Box 242, Folder 2590)
      - Board Members Organization, 1955-1956 (Box 242, Folder 2591)
    - Connecticut Regional Blood Program, 1955-1956 (Box 242, Folder 2592)
    - Connecticut Association for Mental Health, 1955-1956 (Box 242, Folder 2593)
    - Connecticut Nutrition Council, 1955-1956 (Box 242, Folder 2594)
    - Connecticut State Medical Society, 1955-1956 (Box 242, Folder 2595)
    - Connecticut Medical Service, Inc., 1955 (Box 242, Folder 2596)
    - New Haven Medical Association, 1955-1956 (Box 242, Folder 2597)
    - Connecticut, State of
      - General, 1955-1956 (Box 243, Folder 2598)
      - Commission on Alcoholism, 1955-1956 (Box 243, Folder 2599)
      - Department of Education, 1955-1956 (Box 243, Folder 2600)
      - Governor, 1955-1956 (Box 243, Folder 2601)
      - Tuberculosis Commission, 1955-1956 (Box 243, Folder 2602)
      - Long Lane School, Board of Directors, 1955-1956 (Box 243, Folder 2603-2604)
      - Long Lane School, Governor"s Commission, 1955-1956 (Box 243, Folder 2605)
      - Department of Health, 1955-1956 (Box 243, Folder 2606-2608)
      - Department of Health, 1955-1956 (Box 244, Folder 2609)
    - Connecticut Commissioner of Health, 1655-1956 (Box 244, Folder 2610)
    - Directors of Health, 1955-1956 (Box 244, Folder 2611)
    - Public Health Council, 1955-1956 (Box 244, Folder 2612-2613)
    - Connecticut Trudeau Society, 1955-1956 (Box 244, Folder 2614)
    - Connecticut Tuberculosis Association, 1955-1956 (Box 244, Folder 2615-2616)
    - Dental Clinic Society of New Haven, 1955-1956 (Box 244, Folder 2617)
    - Health Departments: local, state and national, 1955-1956 (Box 245, Folder 2618-2620)
    - New York State Health Department, 1955-1956 (Box 245, Folder 2621)
    - New York City Health Department, 1955-1956 (Box 246, Folder 2622)
    - Health Information Foundation, 1955-1956 (Box 246, Folder 2623)
    - Human Relations Area Files, Inc., 1955-1956 (Box 246, Folder 2624)
    - Institute of Inter-American Affairs, 1955-1956 (Box 246, Folder 2625)
    - Publishers, 1955-1956 (Box 246, Folder 2628)
    - Publishers, 1955-1956 (Box 247, Folder 2629-2630)
    - National Association for Mental Health, 1955-1956 (Box 247, Folder 2631)
    - National Citizens Committee for Educational Television, 1955-1956 (Box 247, Folder 2632)
    - National Education Association, 1955-1956 (Box 247, Folder 2633)
    - National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis, 1955-1956 (Box 247, Folder 2634)
    - National Health Council, 1955-1956 (Box 247, Folder 2635-2636)
    - National Health Council, 1955-1956 (Box 248, Folder 2637-2638)
    - National League for Nursing, 1955-1956 (Box 248, Folder 2639)
    - National Publicity Council for Health and Welfare Services, 1955-1956 (Box 248, Folder 2640)
    - National Research Council, 1955-1956 (Box 248, Folder 2641)
      - Committee on Information, 1955-1956 (Box 248, Folder 2642)
    - National Sanitation Foundation, 1955-1956 (Box 249, Folder 2643)
    - National Safety Council, 1955-1956 (Box 249, Folder 2644)
    - National Social Welfare Assembly, 1955-1956 (Box 249, Folder 2645-2646)
    - National Society for the Prevention of Blindness, 1955-1956 (Box 249, Folder 2647-2648)
      - Connecticut Chapter, 1955-1956 (Box 249, Folder 2649)
    - Committee to Protect Our Children"s Teeth, 1955-1956 (Box 249, Folder 2650)
    - National Tuberculosis Association, 1955-1956 (Box 250, Folder 2651-2652)
    - Tuberculosis and Health Association: New Haven, 1955-1956 (Box 250, Folder 2653)
    - New England Health Institute, 1955-1956 (Box 250, Folder 2654)
    - New Haven, general, 1955-1956 (Box 250, Folder 2656)
    - New Haven, Office of the Mayor, 1955-1956 (Box 250, Folder 2656)
    - New Haven Area Rehabilitation Center, Inc., 1955-1956 (Box 250, Folder 2657)
    - New Haven Citizens Action Commission, 1955-1956 (Box 250, Folder 2658)
    - Tuberculosis Commission, 1955-1956 (Box 250, Folder 2659)
    - New Haven Health Departments, 1955-1956 (Box 250, Folder 2660)
    - New Haven City Department of Health, 1955-1956 (Box 251, Folder 2661)
    - Board of Health: minutes, 1955-1956 (Box 251, Folder 2662)
    - New Haven Council of Social Agencies, 1955-1956 (Box 251, Folder 2663)
    - Health Division, Council of Social Agencies, 1955-1956 (Box 251, Folder 2664)
    - New Haven Visiting Nurse Association, 1955-1956 (Box 251, Folder 2665)
    - Association of Schools of Public Health, 1955-1956 (Box 251, Folder 2667)
      - Committee on Public Health Education, correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 252, Folder 2668-2669)
      - Committee on Public Health Education reports, 1955-1956 (Box 252, Folder 2670)
    - California, University of, 1955-1956 (Box 252, Folder 2671)
    - Columbia University, 1955-1956 (Box 252, Folder 2672)
    - Harvard University, 1955-1956 (Box 252, Folder 2673)
    - Johns Hopkins University of, 1955-1956 (Box 252, Folder 2674)
    - Michigan University of, 1955-1956 (Box 252, Folder 2675)
    - Minnesota, University of, 1955-1956 (Box 252, Folder 2676)
    - North Carolina, University of, 1955-1956 (Box 252, Folder 2677)
    - Pittsburgh, University of, 1955-1956 (Box 253, Folder 2678)
    - Puerto Rico, 1955-1956 (Box 253, Folder 2679)
    - Toronto, University of, 1955-1956 (Box 253, Folder 2680)
    - Tulane University, 1956 (Box 253, Folder 2681)
    - Society of Public Health Educators, 1955-1956 (Box 253, Folder 2682)
    - United States Government: general, 1955-1956 (Box 253, Folder 2683)
    - United States Armed Forces, 1955-1956 (Box 253, Folder 2684)
    - United States Department of Agriculture, 1955-1956 (Box 253, Folder 2685)
    - International Cooperation Administration, 1955-1956 (Box 253, Folder 2686)
    - President"s Conference on the Physical Fitness of American Youth, 1955-1956 (Box 253, Folder 2687-2688)
    - United States Department of Health Education and Welfare: general, 1955-1956 (Box 253, Folder 2689)
    - United States Public Health Service, 1955-1956 (Box 254, Folder 2690)
      - National Cancer Institute, 1955-1956 (Box 254, Folder 2691)
      - National Heart Association, 1955-1956 (Box 254, Folder 2692)
      - Division of International Health, 1954-1957 (Box 254, Folder 2693)
      - National Mental Health Institute, 1955-1956 (Box 254, Folder 2694)
      - Division of State Services, 1955-1956 (Box 254, Folder 2695)
    - Veterans Administration: general, 1955 (Box 254, Folder 2696)
    - World Health Organization: general, 1955-1956 (Box 254, Folder 2697-2698)
    - World Health Organization: National Citizens Committee, 1955-1956 (Box 254, Folder 2699)
    - World Health Organization: Pan-American Study Bureau, 1955-1956 (Box 255, Folder 2700)
    - World Health Organization: Study Group on Measurement of Levels of Health, 1955 (Box 255, Folder 2701)
    - National Conference for Cooperation in Health Education, 1955-1956 (Box 255, Folder 2702)
    - Association for Retarded Children in Greater New Haven, 1955-1956 (Box 255, Folder 2703)
    - Gaylord Farm Sanitorium, 1955-1956 (Box 255, Folder 2704-2705)
  - 1956-1957
    - A General, 1956-1957 (Box 256, Folder 2706-2709)
    - B General, 1956-1957 (Box 256, Folder 2710)
    - Bliss, Miss Susan, 1955-1957 (Box 256, Folder 2711-2712)
    - Blumenthal, Andre, 1954-1957 (Box 256, Folder 2713-2715)
    - Bunnell, Mrs. Sterling, 1955-1957 (Box 256, Folder 2716-2717)
    - Bunnell, Mr. and Mrs. Sterling, 1954-1955 (Box 256, Folder 2718)
    - Sterling House Report, 1954-1955 (Box 256, Folder 2719)
    - C General, 1956-1957 (Box 257, Folder 2720-2722)
    - C General, 1956-1957 (Box 257, Folder 2723-2726)
    - Canada, 1956-1957 (Box 257, Folder 2727)
    - D General, 1956-1957 (Box 258, Folder 2728-2729)
    - E General, 1956-1957 (Box 258, Folder 2730)
    - England, 1956-1957 (Box 258, Folder 2731)
      - Dr. Hugh Paul, 1956-1957 (Box 258, Folder 2732)
    - F General, 1956-1957 (Box 258, Folder 2733)
    - Fellowships, 1956-1957 (Box 258, Folder 2734)
    - Films, 1956-1957 (Box 258, Folder 2735)
    - G General, 1956-1957 (Box 258, Folder 2736)
    - H General, 1956-1957 (Box 259, Folder 2737)
    - Hawaii, 1956-1957 (Box 259, Folder 2738-2739)
    - Highlights, 1956-1957 (Box 259, Folder 2740)
    - I General, 1956-1957 (Box 259, Folder 2741-2742)
    - J General, 1956-1957 (Box 259, Folder 2743)
    - K General, 1956-1957 (Box 259, Folder 2744)
    - L General, 1956-1957 (Box 259, Folder 2745)
    - M General, 1956-1957 (Box 260, Folder 2746-2747)
    - N General, 1956-1957 (Box 260, Folder 2748-2751)
    - New Canaan, 1956-1957 (Box 260, Folder 2752)
    - Newspaper clippings, miscellaneous, 1956-1957 (Box 260, Folder 2753)
    - O General, 1956-1957 (Box 260, Folder 2754)
    - P General, 1956-1957 (Box 261, Folder 2755-2758)
    - Puerto Rico - general correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 261, Folder 2759)
    - R General, 1956-1957 (Box 261, Folder 2760-2761)
    - S General, 1956-1957 (Box 261, Folder 2762)
    - T General, 1956-1957 (Box 261, Folder 2763)
    - U General, 1956-1957 (Box 262, Folder 2764-2765)
    - Universities and colleges other than Yale and the Association of Schools of Public Health, 1956-1957 (Box 262, Folder 2766-2767)
    - V General, 1956-1957 (Box 262, Folder 2768)
    - Visitors, 1956-1957 (Box 262, Folder 2769)
    - W General, 1956-1957 (Box 262, Folder 2770-2771)
    - Winslow, Charles Edward A., 1954-1956 (Box 262, Folder 2772-2773)
    - Winslow, Charles Edward A., 1956-1957 (Box 263, Folder 2774)
    - Winslow Lecture, 1955-1957 (Box 263, Folder 2775-2777)
    - Y General, 1956-1957 (Box 263, Folder 2778)
    - Z General, 1956-1957 (Box 263, Folder 2779)
    - Yale University - general, 1956-1957 (Box 263, Folder 2780-2782)
    - Department of Anatomy, 1956-1957 (Box 263, Folder 2783)
    - Department of Applied Physiology, 1956-1957 (Box 263, Folder 2784)
    - Department of the History of Medicine, 1956-1957 (Box 263, Folder 2785)
    - School of Law, 1956-1957 (Box 263, Folder 2786)
    - School of Nursing, 1956-1957 (Box 264, Folder 2787)
    - Department of Political Science, 1956-1957 (Box 264, Folder 2788)
    - Department of Psychiatry, 1956-1957 (Box 264, Folder 2789)
    - Department of Sociology, 1956-1957 (Box 264, Folder 2790)
    - Department of University Health, 1956-1957 (Box 264, Folder 2791)
    - Department of University Health, 1919-1934 (Box 264, Folder 2792)
    - President, Yale University, 1956-1957 (Box 264, Folder 2793)
    - Secretary, Yale University, 1956-1957 (Box 264, Folder 2794)
    - Treasurer, Yale University, 1956-1957 (Box 264, Folder 2795)
    - Provost, Yale University, 1956-1957 (Box 264, Folder 2796)
    - Budget, 1956-1957 (Box 264, Folder 2797)
    - Recommendations for appointment, 1955-1957 (Box 264, Folder 2798-2799)
    - Recommendations for appointment, 1954-1955 (Box 264, Folder 2800)
    - Dean, School of Medicine, 1956-1957 (Box 264, Folder 2801-2802)
    - Assistant Dean, School of Medicine, (Admissions), 1956-1957 (Box 265, Folder 2803)
    - Assistant Dean, School of Medicine, 1956-1957 (Box 265, Folder 2804)
    - Registrar, School of Medicine, 1956-1957 (Box 265, Folder 2805-2806)
    - Registrar, Medical School, 1953-1954 (Box 265, Folder 2807)
    - Business Manager, Medical School, 1956-1957 (Box 265, Folder 2809)
    - Staff meetings, Department of Public Health, 1956-1957 (Box 265, Folder 2810)
    - Executive Secretary, School of Medicine, 1956-1957 (Box 265, Folder 2811)
    - Board of Permanent Officers, 1956-1957 (Box 265, Folder 2812)
    - Executive Committee, 1956-1957 (Box 266, Folder 2813-2814)
    - Medical Library and Yale Journal of Biology and Medicine, 1956-1957 (Box 266, Folder 2815)
    - Dean, Graduate School, 1956-1957 (Box 266, Folder 2816)
    - Assistant Dean, Graduate School, 1956-1957 (Box 266, Folder 2817)
    - Registrar, Graduate Center, 1956-1957 (Box 266, Folder 2818)
    - Yale-New Haven Medical Center, 1956-1957 (Box 266, Folder 2819)
    - Grace-New Haven Community Hospital, 1956-1957 (Box 266, Folder 2820)
    - New Haven Rheumatic Fever and Cardiac program, 1956-1957 (Box 266, Folder 2821)
    - Minutes, Student Council, 1946 (Box 266, Folder 2822)
    - Department of Public Health general, 1956-1957 (Box 266, Folder 2823)
    - Hospital Administration Section, 1956-1957 (Box 266, Folder 2824)
    - Occupational Health, 1956-1957 (Box 267, Folder 2825)
    - Secretarial Staff, 1956-1957 (Box 267, Folder 2826)
    - Annual Report, 1956-1957 (Box 267, Folder 2827)
    - Alumni, 1956-1957 (Box 267, Folder 2828)
    - Alumni Records, 1956 (Box 267, Folder 2829)
    - Field trips, 1956-1957 (Box 267, Folder 2830)
    - Candidates for jobs, 1956-1957 (Box 267, Folder 2831)
    - Requests for candidates for jobs, 1956-1957 (Box 267, Folder 2832-2833)
    - Request for candidates for jobs, 1956-1957 (Box 268, Folder 2834)
    - Ladies Aid, 1956-1957 (Box 268, Folder 2835)
    - American Bureau for Medical Aid to China, 1956-1957 (Box 268, Folder 2836-2837)
    - American Cancer Society
      - Connecticut Division, 1956-1957 (Box 268, Folder 2838)
      - Special study, 1956-1957 (Box 268, Folder 2839)
      - Other division, 1956-1957 (Box 268, Folder 2840)
    - American Dental Association, 1956-1957 (Box 268, Folder 2841)
    - American Heart Association, 1956-1957 (Box 268, Folder 2842)
      - Connecticut Chapter, 1956-1957 (Box 268, Folder 2843)
      - New Haven Chapter, 1956-1957 (Box 268, Folder 2844)
    - American Medical association, 1956-1957 (Box 269, Folder 2845-2848)
    - American Public Health Association, 1956-1957 (Box 269, Folder 2849-2852)
      - Accreditation, 1956-1957 (Box 270, Folder 2853)
      - Committee on Eligibility, 1956-1957 (Box 270, Folder 2854)
      - Annual meeting, 1956-1957 (Box 270, Folder 2855)
      - American Journal of Public Health, 1956-1957 (Box 270, Folder 2856)
      - Committee on Professional Education, 1956-1957 (Box 270, Folder 2857)
      - Ira V. Hiscock, 1956 Address, 1956-1957 (Box 270, Folder 2858)
      - Southern Branch, 1956-1957 (Box 270, Folder 2859)
      - Southern Branch, 1956-1957 (Box 270, Folder 2860)
      - Nominating Committee, 1956-1957 (Box 270, Folder 2861)
      - Professional Examinations Service Monthly Reports, 1956-1957 (Box 270, Folder 2862)
      - Governing Council, 1956-1957 (Box 270, Folder 2863)
      - Financial statements, 1956-1957 (Box 270, Folder 2864)
      - Special Task Force October 12-15, 1956, 1956-1957 (Box 270, Folder 2865-2866)
      - Special Task Force October 12-15, 1956, 1956-1957 (Box 271, Folder 2867-2868)
      - Task Force, 1956-1957 (Box 271, Folder 2869)
      - Committee on administrative Practice, 1956-1957 (Box 271, Folder 2870)
      - State and Local Health Administration, 1956-1957 (Box 271, Folder 2871)
      - Subcommittee on Medical Care, 1956-1957 (Box 271, Folder 2872)
    - American Red Cross, 1956-1957 (Box 271, Folder 2873)
    - Boy Scouts of America, 1956-1957 (Box 271, Folder 2874-2875)
      - Quinnipiac Council, 1956-1957 (Box 271, Folder 2876)
    - Civil Defense, local, state, and national, 1956-1957 (Box 271, Folder 2877)
    - Cleveland Health Museum, 1956-1957 (Box 271, Folder 2878)
    - National Budget Committee, 1956-1957 (Box 272, Folder 2882-2884)
    - National Committee on Alcoholism, 1956-1957 (Box 272, Folder 2885)
    - Connecticut Advisory Council on School Health, 1956-1957 (Box 272, Folder 2886)
    - Connecticut Health League, 1956-1957 (Box 272, Folder 2887)
    - Connecticut Public Health Association, 1956-1957 (Box 273, Folder 2888)
    - Board members, Connecticut Public Health Nursing Association, 1956-1957 (Box 273, Folder 2889)
    - Connecticut Regional Blood Program, 1956-1957 (Box 273, Folder 2890)
    - Connecticut Association of Mental Health, 1956-1957 (Box 273, Folder 2891)
    - Connecticut Nutrition Council, 1956-1957 (Box 273, Folder 2892)
    - Connecticut State Medical Society, 1956-1957 (Box 273, Folder 2893)
    - Connecticut State Medical Journal, 1956-1957 (Box 273, Folder 2894)
    - Connecticut, State of
      - General, 1956-1957 (Box 273, Folder 2895)
      - Education, Department of, 1956-1957 (Box 273, Folder 2896)
      - Governor, 1956-1957 (Box 273, Folder 2897)
      - Tuberculosis Commission, 1956-1957 (Box 273, Folder 2898)
      - Long Lane School, Board of Directors, 1956-1957 (Box 273, Folder 2899)
      - Long Lane School, Board of directors, 1956-1957 (Box 274, Folder 2900-2902)
      - Long Lane School, Governor"s Commission, 1956-1957 (Box 274, Folder 2903)
      - Health, Department of, 1956-1957 (Box 274, Folder 2904-2905)
      - Health, Department of, 1956-1957 (Box 275, Folder 2906-2908)
    - Commissioner of Health, 1956-1957 (Box 275, Folder 2909)
    - Directors of Health, 1956-1957 (Box 275, Folder 2910)
    - Public Health Council, 1956-1957 (Box 275, Folder 2911)
    - Public Health Council, 1956-1957 (Box 276, Folder 2912-2914)
    - Connecticut Trudeau Society, 1956-1957 (Box 276, Folder 2915)
    - Connecticut Tuberculosis Association, 1956-1957 (Box 276, Folder 2916)
    - Dental Clinic Society of New Haven, 1956-1957 (Box 276, Folder 2917)
    - Health Department, local, state and national, 1956-1957 (Box 276, Folder 2918-2919)
    - Health Department, local, state and national, 1956-1957 (Box 277, Folder 2920-2923)
    - New York State Health Department, 1956-1957 (Box 277, Folder 2924)
    - New York City Health Department, 1956-1957 (Box 277, Folder 2925)
    - Health Information Foundation, 1956-1957 (Box 277, Folder 2926)
    - Human Relations Area Files Incorporated, 1956-1957 (Box 277, Folder 2927-2928)
    - Institute of Inter-American Affairs, 1956-1957 (Box 277, Folder 2929)
    - Publishers, 1956-1957 (Box 278, Folder 2933)
    - National Association for Mental Health, 1956-1957 (Box 278, Folder 2934)
    - National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis, 1956-1957 (Box 278, Folder 2935)
    - National Health Council, 1956-1957 (Box 278, Folder 2936-2940)
    - National League for Nursing, 1956-1957 (Box 279, Folder 2941-2942)
    - National Publicity Council for Health and Welfare Services, Incorporated, 1956-1957 (Box 279, Folder 2943)
    - National Research Council, 1956-1957 (Box 279, Folder 2944)
    - National Sanitation Foundation, 1956-1957 (Box 279, Folder 2945-2946)
    - National Safety Council, 1956-1957 (Box 279, Folder 2947)
    - National Social Welfare Assembly, 1956-1957 (Box 279, Folder 2948-2949)
    - National Society for the Prevention of Blindness, 1956-1957 (Box 280, Folder 2950-2952)
    - Special Project - Prevention of Blindness and Conservation of Vision, 1956-1957 (Box 280, Folder 2953)
    - New York Committee on Children"s Teeth, 1956-1957 (Box 280, Folder 2954)
    - National Tuberculosis Association, 1956-1957 (Box 280, Folder 2955-2958)
    - National Tuberculosis Association, 1956-1957 (Box 281, Folder 2959)
      - Evaluation Guide, 1956-1957 (Box 281, Folder 2960)
      - Program and budget, 1956-1957 (Box 281, Folder 2961)
      - Board, 1956-1957 (Box 281, Folder 2962)
    - Tuberculosis Nursing Advisory Service of the National League of Nursing, 1956-1957 (Box 281, Folder 2963)
    - New Haven Tuberculosis and Health Association, 1956-1957 (Box 281, Folder 2964)
    - New Haven, City of, general, 1956-1957 (Box 281, Folder 2965)
    - New Haven, City of, Mayor"s office, 1956-1957 (Box 281, Folder 2966)
    - New Haven Area Rehabilitation Center, 1956-1957 (Box 281, Folder 2967)
    - Citizen"s Action Commission, 1956-1957 (Box 281, Folder 2968)
    - Tuberculosis Advisory Commission of the Greater New Haven Area, 1956-1957 (Box 281, Folder 2969)
    - New Haven, City of, Health Department of, 1956-1957 (Box 281, Folder 2970)
    - New Haven, City of, Health Department of, 1956-1957 (Box 282, Folder 2971-2972)
    - Minutes of meeting, 1956-1957 (Box 282, Folder 2973)
    - The Blind Survey, 1956-1957 (Box 282, Folder 2974)
    - New Haven Council of Social Agencies, 1956-1957 (Box 282, Folder 2975)
    - Health Division Council of Social Agencies, 1956-1957 (Box 282, Folder 2976)
    - New Haven Visiting Nurse association, 1956-1957 (Box 282, Folder 2977)
    - Association of School of Public Health
      - Committee on Health Education, 1954-1955 (Box 282, Folder 2979)
      - Committee on Public Health Education, 1954-1955 (Box 282, Folder 2980)
      - Committee on Public Health Education, 1954-1955 (Box 283, Folder 2981)
      - Third Report of Teaching of Health Education, 1956-1957 (Box 283, Folder 2982)
    - Schools of Public Health, Association of, 1954-1955 (Box 283, Folder 2983-2984)
      - Report of Committee on Health Education, 1955 (Box 283, Folder 2985)
      - Committee on Health Education, 1956-1957 (Box 283, Folder 2986-2987)
    - Schools of Public Health, Association of, 1956-1957 (Box 284, Folder 2988-2991)
    - Committee on Army Medical Education, 1956-1957 (Box 284, Folder 2992)
    - California, 1956-1957 (Box 284, Folder 2993)
    - Columbia, 1956-1957 (Box 284, Folder 2994)
    - Summaries of Current Research Projects in Health Administration, 1956-1957 (Box 284, Folder 2995)
    - Harvard, 1956-1957 (Box 284, Folder 2996)
    - Johns Hopkins, 1956-1957 (Box 284, Folder 2997)
    - Michigan, 1956-1957 (Box 284, Folder 2998-2999)
    - Minnesota, 1956-1957 (Box 284, Folder 3000)
    - Montreal, 1956-1957 (Box 284, Folder 3001)
    - North Carolina, 1956-1957 (Box 284, Folder 3002)
    - Pittsburgh, 1956-1957 (Box 284, Folder 3003)
    - Puerto Rico, 1956-1957 (Box 284, Folder 3004)
    - Toronto, 1956-1957 (Box 285, Folder 3005)
    - Tulane, 1956-1957 (Box 285, Folder 3006)
    - Society of Public Health Educators, 1956-1957 (Box 285, Folder 3007)
    - United States Government, general, 1956-1957 (Box 285, Folder 3008)
    - United States Armed Forces, 1956-1957 (Box 285, Folder 3009)
    - United States Armed Forces, 1956-1957 (Box 286, Folder 3010)
    - United States Department of Agriculture, 1956-1957 (Box 286, Folder 3011)
    - United States Census Bureau, 1956-1957 (Box 286, Folder 3012)
    - International Cooperation Administration, 1956-1957 (Box 286, Folder 3013)
    - United States Department of Health Education and Welfare, general, 1956-1957 (Box 286, Folder 3014)
    - United States Public Health Service, 1956-1957 (Box 286, Folder 3015-3018)
    - United States Public Health Service, 1956-1957 (Box 287, Folder 3019)
      - National Cancer Institute, 1956-1957 (Box 287, Folder 3020)
      - National Heart Association, 1956-1957 (Box 287, Folder 3021)
      - International Health, Division of, 1956-1957 (Box 287, Folder 3022)
      - National Mental Health Institute, 1956-1957 (Box 287, Folder 3023)
      - State Services, Division of, 1956-1957 (Box 287, Folder 3024)
    - World Health Organization
      - General, 1956-1957 (Box 287, Folder 3025-3026)